Streib, Victor; Papers apap330
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1947-2012, Undated; 1; 19 cubic ft.
  - Executed Women, United States, 1947-2008, Undated; 1.1; 4 cubic ft.
    - Pennsylvania: Elizabeth Erwin, executed 1765-09-26, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Pennsylvania: Jane Ewing, executed 1765-01-29, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Pennsylvania: Catharine Fisher, executed 1779-06-05, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Pennsylvania: Elizabeth Graul, executed 1759-03-10, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Pennsylvania: Martha Grinder, executed 1866-01-19, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Pennsylvania: Charlotte jonex, executed 1858-02-12, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania: Mary Kennedy, executed 1768-12-24, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania: Catherine Krebs, executed 1767-12-19, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania: Catherine C. Miller, executed 1881-02-03, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania: Hannah Miller, executed 1805-08-01, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania: Lena Miller, executed 1867-11-13, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania: Elizabeth Moore, executed 1809-05-27, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania: Rebecca Moss, executed 1745-10-07, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania: Elizabeth Murphy, executed executed 1724-07-13, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania: Ann Ottley, executed 1742, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania: Phebe, executed 1764-03, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania: Elizabeth Rimby, executed 1806-09-03, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania: Elizabeth Robinson, executed 1750-02-01, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania: Eve Mary Schmidt, executed 1755, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania: Irene Schroeder, executed 1931-02-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania: Corinne Sykes, executed 1946-10-14, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania: Mary Twigg, executed 1858-10-22, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania: Unknown, 1732, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania: Sarah Jane Whiteling, executed 1889-06-25, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania: Elizabeth Wilson, executed 1786-01-03, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Puerto Rico: Unknown, 1849-04-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Rhode Island: general, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Rhode Island: Anne Allen, executed 1737-11-04, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Rhode Island: Jenny Chapman, executed 1767, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Rhode Island: Hannah Degoe, executed 1710-11-29, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Rhode Island: Uknown, executed 1687-10-27, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - South Carolina: general, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - South Carolina: Sarah Chamberlain, executed 1738, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - South Carolina: Ann Connolly, executed 1788, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - South Carolina: Lavinia Fisher, executed 1820-02-18, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - South Carolina: Ada Hiers, executed 1893-07-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - South Carolina: Kate, executed 1741, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - South Carolina: Sue Stidham Logue, executed 1943-01-15, 1985; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - South Carolina: Rhodie, executed 1861-10, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - South Carolina: Rose, executed 1853, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - South Carolina: Slave, executed 1754-06-24, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - South Carolina: Slave, 1761-01-14, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - South Carolina: Slave, executed 1825-02-24, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - South Carolina: Slave, executed 1850, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - South Carolina: Slaves, executed 1851-06-13, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - South Carolina: Rose Marie Stinette, executed 1947-01-17, 1985; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - South Carolina: Lucinda Teasdale, executed 1882-06-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - South Carolina: Anna Tribble, executed 1892-20-07, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Tennessee: Black Woman, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Tennessee: Black Woman 1819, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Tennessee: Harriet, executed 1833-08-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Tennessee: Mrs. Hughes, executed 1837, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Tennessee: Eve Martin, executed 1820, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Tennessee: Molly, executed 1807-03-20, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Tennessee: Slave, executed 1808, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Texas: Betty Lou Beets, executed 2000-02-24, 1989; 1995; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Texas: Betty Lou Beets, executed 2000-02-24, 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Texas: Lucy, executed 1858-03-05, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Texas: Jane Elkins, executed 1854, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Texas: Frances Elaine Newton, executed 2005-09-14, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Texas: Chipita Rodriguez, executed 1863-11-13, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Texas: Karla Fay Tucker, executed 1998-02-03, 1992; 1994; 1997; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Texas: Karla Fay Tucker, executed 1998-02-03, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Virginia: general, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Virginia: Agnes, executed 1864-09-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Virginia: Amelia, executed 1856-09-12, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Virginia: Amey, executed 1799-06-15, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Virginia: Amy, executed 1812-12-11, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Virginia: Angelina, executed 1859-09-30, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Virginia: Ann, executed 1860-03-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Virginia: Anna, executed 1856-06-20, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Virginia: Annia, executed 1829-10-21, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Virginia: Bet, executed 1863, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Virginia: Besty, executed 1840-09-25, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Virginia: Blair, executed 1738-05, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Virginia: Elizabeth Bolton, executed 1770, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Virginia: Sussanna Brazier, executed 1775-01-13, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Virginia: Bridget, executed 1704, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Virginia: Margaret Buckner, executed 1853-08-12, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Virginia: Catharine, executed 1857-08-21, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Virginia: Sarah Capps, 1868-07-24, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Virginia: Caty, executed 188-01-30, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Virginia: Celia, executed 1821-08-15, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Virginia: Chainey, executed 1800, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Virginia: Jane Champion, executed 1632, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Virginia: Chaney, executed 1820-01-21, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Virginia: Charlotte, executed 1806-03-15, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Virginia: Chastity, executed 1803-10-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Virginia: Chloe, executed 1795-11-27, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Virginia: Virginia Christian, executed 1912-08-16, 1985; 2003; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Virginia: Clara, executed 1816-10-14, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Virginia: Crease, executed 1806, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Virginia: Daphne, executed 1739-08-02, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Virginia: Delph, executed 1818-07-26, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Virginia: Eliza, executed 1849-10-12, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Virginia: Eliza, executed 1860-03-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Virginia: Elizabeth, executed 1832-01, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Virginia: Esther, executed 1767-05-19, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Virginia: Eve, executed 1746-01-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Virginia: Fanny, executed 1806-02-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Virginia: Fanny, executed 1832-10-05, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Virginia: Fannie, executed 1858, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Virginia: Flora, executed 1809-05-05, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Virginia: Lucinda Fowlkes, executed 1712, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Virginia: Elizabeth Gordon, executed 1712, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Virginia: Elizabeth Greenley, executed 1736-11-26, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Virginia: Margaret Hatch, executed 1633, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Virginia: Elizabeth Hazel, executed 1790-10-21, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Virginia: Jane, executed 1852-09-10, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Virginia: Jane, executed 1858-09-10, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Virginia: Jenny, executed 1858-02-26, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Virginia: Judith, executed 1772-06-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Virginia: Judy, executed 1827-10-26, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Virginia: Margaret Lashley, executed 1892-01-22, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Virginia: Teresa Lewis, executed 2010-09-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Virginia: Lucinda, executed 1838-09-24, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Virginia: Lucy, executed 1742-06-30, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Virginia: Lucy, executed 1749-05, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Virginia: Lucy, executed 1855-06-15, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Virginia: Mahalia, executed 1852-05-14, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Virginia: Margaret, executed 1863-01-09, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Virginia: Emmeline Meaker, 1883-03-30, 1985; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Virginia: Mary Mabel Rodgers, executed 1905-12-08, 1985; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Virginia: Mary, executed 1833-06-21, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Virginia: Elizabeth Maze, executed 1739-11-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Virginia: Barbara Miller, executed 1883-09-14, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Virginia: Moll, executed 1783, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - Virginia: Moll, executed 1791-0707-08, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Virginia: Moll, executed 1796-11-12, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Virginia: Molly, executed 1826-07, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 125)
    - Virginia: Molly, executed 1852-09-10, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 126)
    - Virginia: Mary Murray, executed 1755-05-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 127)
    - Virginia: Henneth Murrel, executed 1891-09-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 128)
    - Virginia: Nan, executed 1763, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 129)
    - Virginia: Nan, executed 1801-04-10, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 130)
    - Virginia: Nancy, executed 1857-11-20, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 131)
    - Virginia: Nelly, executed 1793-10-04, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 132)
    - Virginia: Nelly, executed 1828-03-17, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 133)
    - Virginia: Nelly, executed 1834-08-01, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 134)
    - Virginia: Nan, executed 1821-11-03, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 135)
    - Virginia: Penelope, executed 1781-04-04, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 136)
    - Virginia: Catherine Peppers, executed 1774-06-03, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 137)
    - Virginia: Phoebe, executed 1836-05-13, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 138)
    - Virginia: Poll, executed 1779-01-22, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 139)
    - Virginia: Polly, executed 1798-03-23, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 140)
    - Virginia: Sall, executed 1773-01-11, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 141)
    - Virginia: Sandy, executed 1829-08-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 142)
    - Virginia: Sarah, executed 1705, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 143)
    - Virginia: Sarah, executed 1818-07-10, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 144)
    - Virginia: Martha Sharp, executed 1767, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 145)
    - Virginia: Slave, executed 1737-02-04, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 146)
    - Virginia: Slaves, executed 1854-02-12, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 147)
    - Virginia: Slave daughter, executed 1857-0213, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 148)
    - Virginia: Mary Snodgrass, executed 1896-07-10, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 149)
    - Virginia: Ann Tandy, executed 1702, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 150)
    - Virginia: Elizabeth Twopence, executed 1739-05, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 151)
    - Virginia: Unknown, executed 1692, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 152)
    - Virginia: Unknown, executed 1737, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 153)
    - Virginia: Violet, executed 1780-03-04, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 154)
    - Virginia: Harriet Wallage, executed 07-17, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 155)
    - Virginia: Jane Williams, executed 1852-09-10, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 156)
    - Virginia: Winny, executed 1769-07-11, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 157)
    - West Virginia: Rebecca Coalter, executed 1825-07-02, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 158)
    - West Virginia: Dolly, executed 1769-07-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 159)
    - West Virginia: Lucy, executed 1832-09-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 160)
    - West Virginia: Millay Robes, executed 1769, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 161)
    - West Virginia: Jane Tygart, executed 1814-11-18, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 162)
  - Sentenced Women, United States, 1983-2012, Undated; 1.2; 4 cubic ft.
    - Alabama: Patricia Blackman, sentenced 2002-04-18, 2002 April (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Alabama: Debra Bracewell, sentenced 1978-05-17, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Alabama: Tierra Gobble, sentenced 2005-10-26, 2006 March (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Alabama: Judith Haney, sentenced 1988-11-18, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Alabama: Louise Harris, sentenced 1989-08-11 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Alabama: Judith Ann Neelley, sentenced 1983-04-18 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Alabama: Christie Scott, sentenced 2009-08-05, 2010; 2012 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Alabama: Shonda Nicole, sentenced 1999-10-22 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Alabama: Patricia Ann Thomas Jackson, sentenced 1981-12-28, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Alabama: Maxine Walker, sentenced 1989, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Arizona: Wendy Andriano, sentenced 2004-12-22, 2005 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Arizona: Doris Carlson, sentenced 2000-03-31 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Arizona: Shawna Forde, sentenced 2011-02-22, 2012 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Arizona: Debra Milke, sentenced 1991-01-18, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Arizona: Debra Milke, sentenced 1991-01-18, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Arkansas: Patricia Hendrickson, sentenced 1984-04-13, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - California: General, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - California: Rosie Alfaro, sentenced 1992-07-14 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - California: Dora Buenrostro, sentenced 1994, 1998; 2002 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - California: Socorro Caro, sentenced 2002-04-05, 2001 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - California: Celeste Simone Carrington, sentenced 1994-11-23, 2002 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - California: Cynthia Coffman, sentenced 1989-08-30, 1990; 2002 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - California: Kerry Lynn Dalton, sentenced 1995-05-23, 1998; 2005; 2007 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - California: Susan Eubanks, sentenced 1999-10-14, 1997; 2002 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - California: Mabel Glenn, sentenced 1975-10-21, 1990; 2005 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - California: Veronica Gonzales, sentenced 1998-07-20, 2002 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - California: Elaine Kozeak, sentenced 1975, rev. 1976, 1997; 2005 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - California: Maureen McDermott, sentenced 1990-06-08, 2002 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - California: Michelle Michard, sentenced 2002-09-25 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - California: Tanya Nelson, sentenced 2010-04-23, 2012 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - California: Sandy Nieves, sentenced 2000-08-09, 2008 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - California: Angelina Rodriguez, sentenced 2004-01-12, 2003 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - California: Brooke Rottiers, sentenced 2010-10-23, 2012 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - California: Mary Ellen Samuels, sentenced 1994-09-16, 2002; 2005 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - California: Cathy Lynn Sarinana, sentenced 2009-06-26, 2010 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - California: Janeen Synder, sentenced 2006-09-07, 2007 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - California: Catherine Thompson, sentenced 1993-06-10, 2002; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - California: Caroline Young, sentenced 1995-10-27, 2001; 2005 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Connecticut: Janet Griffin, sentenced 1996-05 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Delaware: Linda Lou Charbonneau, sentenced 2004-06-04 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Federal: Valerie Friend, con. 2007 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Federal: Angela Johnson, sentenced 2005-12-20, 2008 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Federal: Lisa Montgomery, sentenced 2007-10-26 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Florida: Margaret Allen, sentenced 2011-05-19, 2010 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Florida: Marie Arrington, sentenced 1968, rev. 1972, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Florida: Carla Caillier, sentenced 1987-03-19, rev. 1988, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Florida: Ana Cardona, sentenced 1992-04-01, 1997; 2002; 2010 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Florida: Emily Carr, sentenced 2011-02-22, 2010; 2012 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Florida: Tiffany Cole, sentenced 2008-03-05, 2007 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Florida: Dee Dyne Casteel, sentenced 1987-07-16, 1989; 1993; 2002 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Florida: Kaysie Dudley, sentenced 1987-01-27, rev. 1989-08-23 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Florida: Bertha Hall, sentenced 1926, rev. 1929, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Florida: Deidre Hunt, sentenced 1990-09-13, rev. 1992-10-15 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Florida: Andrea Hicks Jackson, sentenced 1984-02-10, rev. 1989, re-sentenced 1992-02-21, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Florida: Billie Jackson, sentenced 1927, rev. 1927, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Florida: Irene Jackson, sentenced 1961, par. 1972, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Florida: Sonia Jacobs, sentenced 1976-08-20, rev. 1981-03-26, Free 1992-10-09, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Florida: Virginia Larzelere, sentenced 1993-05-11, 1998; 2005 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Florida: Ruby McCollum, sentenced 1952, rel. 1974, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Georgia: Janice Buttrum, sentenced 1981-08-31, 1986; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Georgia: Emma Cunningham, sentenced 1979-10-26, rel. 1990-11-30, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Georgia: Kelly Gissendaner, sentenced 1998-11-20, 1997; 2005; 2007 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Georgia: Rebecca (Machetti) Smith, sentenced 1975-01-30, rev. 1983[?], Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Georgia: Shirley Tyler, sentenced 1979-12-04, rev. 1986[?], Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Georgia: Teresa Whittington, sentenced 1982-05-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Idaho: Robin Row, sentenced 1993-12, 1999; 2003 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Idaho: Karla Windsor, sentenced 1984-02-28, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Illinois: Guinevere Garcia, sentenced 1992-10-09, rev. 1996-01-16 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Illinois: Bernina Mata, sentenced 1999-10-28, 2000; 2003; 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Illinois: Marilyn Mulero, sentenced 1993-11-12, rev. 1997-05-22, 1999; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Illinois: Latasha Pulliam, sentenced 1994-06-15, 2003 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Illinois: Geraldine Smith, sentenced 1991-02-20, rev. 1997-06-19, 1998; 2003 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Illinois: Dorothy Williams, sentenced 1991-04-18, 2001; 2003 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Illinois: Jacqueline Williams, sentenced 1998-03-21, 1999; 2003 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Indiana: Debra Brown, sentenced 1986-06-23, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Indiana: Paula Cooper, sentenced 1986-07-11, 2006; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Indiana: Paula Cooper, Appellant Brief, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Indiana: Paula Cooper, Brief of Amicus Curiae, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Indiana: Paula Cooper, Supreme Court Briefs, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Indiana: Paula Cooper, Trial Documents, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Indiana: Paula Cooper, Trial Documents, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Indiana: Paula Cooper, Sentencing Hearing Transcript, 1986 July 11 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Indiana: Paula Cooper, Clippings, 1987; 2003 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Indiana: Cindy Lou Landress, sentenced 1989-06-26, rev. 1993-03-18, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Indiana: Lois Thacker, sentenced 1985-06-27, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Kentucky: Virginia Caudill, sentenced 2000-03-24, 2003; 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Kentucky: Lafunda Fay Foster, sentenced 1989-04-24, rev. 1992-12-19 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Kentucky: Laverne O'Bryan, sentenced 1980-09-12, rev. 1982, 2006; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)